<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><ads><Laptop identity="\MSI GE70"><price>680</price><size>17</size><name>MSI GE70 17 inch GAMING LAPTOP-- i7 -- NVIDIA-- GAMES ON HIGH!!</name><description>Model is in good condition, never had a single problem.

Comes with a fresh install of Windows 10 HOME!!
Also comes with original box and charger.

Specs are as follows:

-Intel Core i7 4710hq @ 2.5 - 2.5ghz QUAD CORE (Very powerful processor)

-12gb ram

-Nvidia GeForce GTX 860m with 2gb dedicated GDDR5 video memory

-Intel HD 4600 integrated graphics for saving battery life, battery is good for 4 hours!!

-1tb HDD, plenty of storage

-17.3inch Full HD 1920 x 1080p matte display, graphics are beauitful

-Dynaudio speakers, sound quality is amazing, easily fills a room.

-Steel Series backlit color changing keyboard

-Atheros Killer ethernet, and Intel AC wireless

-HDMI, CD/DVD, USB 3.0, ect
---------------------

Very powerful gaming laptop from MSI, surprisingly thin and portable.
Great specs and powerful components, perfect for school with the portable power and great screen.

Model is GE70 - 2PE

Asking $680 OBO
</description><zip>t2z1x8</zip><active>0</active></Laptop><Laptop identity="\MSI GT70"><price>680</price><size>17</size><name>MSI GT70 GAMING LAPTOP-- i7 --24gb ram-- 2x SSD-- Nvidia</name><description>Model is in great condition, never had a single problem.

Will run games on high/ultra settings!!
Comes with a fresh install of Windows 10 Pro!!

Specs are as follows:
----------------------

-Intel Core i7 4700mq @ 2.4 - 3.4ghz QUAD CORE

-24gb DDR3 ram

-Nvidia GeForce GTX 770m with 3gb dedicated GDDR5 video memory, WILL PLAY GAMES ON HIGH SETTINGS!!!

-Intel Integrated HD 4600 graphics for saving battery life, battery is good for 3-4hours!!

-2 x 128gb SSDs in RAID-0 array. (256gb total) BOOTS IN 3 SECONDS!! Everything loads instantly.

-17.3inch FULL HD 1920 x 1080p matte display, beautiful graphics!!

-Atheros Killer wireless 1202-n, very fast wireless adapter, loads web-pages instantly!!, Also has Atheros Killer Ethernet for a very fast wires connection.

-SteelSeries backlit color changing gaming keyboard

-DynAudio speakers with built-in subwoofer for amazing sound quality!! Easily fills a room.

-CD/DVD/Bluray combo dive, HDMI, USB 3.0, HD webcam ect.
--------------------------------

Very powerful MSI gaming laptop boots instantly, and will run all content. Loads webpages and programs instantly as well.

Great for gaming, or school, with a high end build quality, good battery life., and great performance.

Originally cost $2500 from MSI

Model is GT70 -2OC Dominator

Asking $680 OBO
</description><zip>t2z1x8</zip><active>0</active></Laptop><Laptop identity="\Dell 5558"><price>420</price><size>15</size><name>Dell 5558 Inspiron --- 15inch laptop -- 1080p IPS-- OFFICE 2016</name><description>Model is in great condition
Comes with a fresh install of Windows 10 PRO,
As well as Microsoft OFFICE 2016 PROFESSIONAL PLUS!!!!
-----------------------

Specs are as follows:

-Intel Core i5 4210u @ 1.7 - 2.7ghz (Fast and efficient)

-Intel HD 4400 integrated graphics, good for very light gaming.

-8gb ram

-1tb HDD

-15.6inch FULL HD 1920 x 1080p IPS display, glossy. Very high color accuracy, graphics are beautiful!!

-Full size backlit keyboard

-USB 3.0, HDMI, CD/DVD, dual band wireless, ect

-Battery is good for 5-7 hours!!
-----------------------------

Very thin laptop from Dell, portable and powerful with a beautiful Full HD display.

Great for work or school with the installation of OFFICE 2016, and great battery life!!

Model is Inspiron 5558 Signature Edition, 
Was $1100, 
asking $420 OBO
</description><zip>t2z1x8</zip><active>1</active></Laptop><Laptop identity="\MSI GE72"><price>780</price><size>17</size><name>MSI GE72 GAMING LAPTOP-- i7-- Nvidia GTX-- GAMES ON HIGH!!</name><description>Model is in mint condition, never had a single problem, looks and works like new.
Comes with a fresh install of Windows 10!!!

Also comes with a brand new battery, currently at 0.0% wear level.

Specs are as follows:
-----------------------------

-Intel Core i7 5700HQ @ 2.7 - 3.5ghz QUAD CORE (Very fast powerful processor)

-12gb ram

-Nvidia GeForce GTX 960m with 2gb dedicated GDDR5 video memory, WILL PLAY GAMES ON HIGH SETTINGS!!!! No lag

-Intel HD 5600 integrated graphics for saving battery life, battery is good for around 5 hours!!

-1tb HDD

-17.3inch FULL HD 1920 x 1080p matte display, graphics are beautiful

-Dynauidio speakers for amazing sound quality, easily fills a room.

-Steelseries color changing gaming keyboard.

-CD/DVD, HDMI, USB 3.0, dual band wifi, killer ethernet, ect.
-----------------------------------

Very powerful gaming laptop from MSI, relatively thin with great battery life, and power on the go.
Perfect for school or work, or anywhere a fast laptop is needed.

Will run games on high settings, and also has a brushed aluminum chassis for high end look and feel, and comes with a brand new battery!!

Model is GE72 2QD
Originally cost $1800, asking $780 OBO
</description><zip>t2z1x8</zip><active>1</active></Laptop></ads>