<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><ads><Laptop identity="\MSI GE70"><price>680</price><size>17</size><name>MSI GE70 17 inch GAMING LAPTOP-- i7 -- NVIDIA-- GAMES ON HIGH!!</name><description>Model is in good condition, never had a single problem.

Comes with a fresh install of Windows 10 HOME!!
Also comes with original box and charger.

Specs are as follows:

-Intel Core i7 4710hq @ 2.5 - 2.5ghz QUAD CORE (Very powerful processor)

-12gb ram

-Nvidia GeForce GTX 860m with 2gb dedicated GDDR5 video memory

-Intel HD 4600 integrated graphics for saving battery life, battery is good for 4 hours!!

-1tb HDD, plenty of storage

-17.3inch Full HD 1920 x 1080p matte display, graphics are beauitful

-Dynaudio speakers, sound quality is amazing, easily fills a room.

-Steel Series backlit color changing keyboard

-Atheros Killer ethernet, and Intel AC wireless

-HDMI, CD/DVD, USB 3.0, ect
---------------------

Very powerful gaming laptop from MSI, surprisingly thin and portable.
Great specs and powerful components, perfect for school with the portable power and great screen.

Model is GE70 - 2PE

Asking $680 OBO
</description><zip>t2z1x8</zip><active>0</active></Laptop><Laptop identity="\MSI GT70"><price>680</price><size>17</size><name>MSI GT70 GAMING LAPTOP-- i7 --24gb ram-- 2x SSD-- Nvidia</name><description>Model is in great condition, never had a single problem.

Will run games on high/ultra settings!!
Comes with a fresh install of Windows 10 Pro!!

Specs are as follows:
----------------------

-Intel Core i7 4700mq @ 2.4 - 3.4ghz QUAD CORE

-24gb DDR3 ram

-Nvidia GeForce GTX 770m with 3gb dedicated GDDR5 video memory, WILL PLAY GAMES ON HIGH SETTINGS!!!

-Intel Integrated HD 4600 graphics for saving battery life, battery is good for 3-4hours!!

-2 x 128gb SSDs in RAID-0 array. (256gb total) BOOTS IN 3 SECONDS!! Everything loads instantly.

-17.3inch FULL HD 1920 x 1080p matte display, beautiful graphics!!

-Atheros Killer wireless 1202-n, very fast wireless adapter, loads web-pages instantly!!, Also has Atheros Killer Ethernet for a very fast wires connection.

-SteelSeries backlit color changing gaming keyboard

-DynAudio speakers with built-in subwoofer for amazing sound quality!! Easily fills a room.

-CD/DVD/Bluray combo dive, HDMI, USB 3.0, HD webcam ect.
--------------------------------

Very powerful MSI gaming laptop boots instantly, and will run all content. Loads webpages and programs instantly as well.

Great for gaming, or school, with a high end build quality, good battery life., and great performance.

Originally cost $2500 from MSI

Model is GT70 -2OC Dominator

Asking $680 OBO
</description><zip>t2z1x8</zip><active>0</active></Laptop><Laptop identity="\Dell 5558"><price>420</price><size>15</size><name>Dell 5558 Inspiron --- 15inch laptop -- 1080p IPS-- OFFICE 2016</name><description>Model is in great condition
Comes with a fresh install of Windows 10 PRO,
As well as Microsoft OFFICE 2016 PROFESSIONAL PLUS!!!!
-----------------------

Specs are as follows:

-Intel Core i5 4210u @ 1.7 - 2.7ghz (Fast and efficient)

-Intel HD 4400 integrated graphics, good for very light gaming.

-8gb ram

-1tb HDD

-15.6inch FULL HD 1920 x 1080p IPS display, glossy. Very high color accuracy, graphics are beautiful!!

-Full size backlit keyboard

-USB 3.0, HDMI, CD/DVD, dual band wireless, ect

-Battery is good for 5-7 hours!!
-----------------------------

Very thin laptop from Dell, portable and powerful with a beautiful Full HD display.

Great for work or school with the installation of OFFICE 2016, and great battery life!!

Model is Inspiron 5558 Signature Edition, 
Was $1100, 
asking $420 OBO
</description><zip>t2z1x8</zip><active>0</active></Laptop><Laptop identity="\MSI GE72"><price>780</price><size>17</size><name>MSI GE72 GAMING LAPTOP-- i7-- Nvidia GTX-- GAMES ON HIGH!!</name><description>Model is in mint condition, never had a single problem, looks and works like new.
Comes with a fresh install of Windows 10!!!

Also comes with a brand new battery, currently at 0.0% wear level.

Specs are as follows:
-----------------------------

-Intel Core i7 5700HQ @ 2.7 - 3.5ghz QUAD CORE (Very fast powerful processor)

-12gb ram

-Nvidia GeForce GTX 960m with 2gb dedicated GDDR5 video memory, WILL PLAY GAMES ON HIGH SETTINGS!!!! No lag

-Intel HD 5600 integrated graphics for saving battery life, battery is good for around 5 hours!!

-1tb HDD

-17.3inch FULL HD 1920 x 1080p matte display, graphics are beautiful

-Dynauidio speakers for amazing sound quality, easily fills a room.

-Steelseries color changing gaming keyboard.

-CD/DVD, HDMI, USB 3.0, dual band wifi, killer ethernet, ect.
-----------------------------------

Very powerful gaming laptop from MSI, relatively thin with great battery life, and power on the go.
Perfect for school or work, or anywhere a fast laptop is needed.

Will run games on high settings, and also has a brushed aluminum chassis for high end look and feel, and comes with a brand new battery!!

Model is GE72 2QD
Originally cost $1800, asking $780 OBO
</description><zip>t2z1x8</zip><active>0</active></Laptop><Laptop identity="\Asus ROG"><price>750</price><size>15</size><name>Asus ROG GAMING LAPTOP-- i7 -Nvidia GTX-- SSD-- 16gb ram</name><description>Model is in good condition, never had a single problem. Comes with a fresh install of Windows 10 PRO

Never had a single problem.

Specs are as follows:
--------------------------

-Intel Core i7 6700HQ @ 2.6 - 3.5ghz QUAD CORE!! (Very powerful processor)

-Nvidia GeForce GTX 960m with 2gb dedicated GDDR5 video memory, GAMES ON HIGH SETTINGS!!

-Intel HD 530 integrated graphics for saving battery life, battery is good for 3-4 hours

-UPGRADED 16gb DDR4 ram, @ 2133mhz (latest generation of memory, very fast with low latency)

-UPGRADED 256gb SSD + 1tb hdd, boots in seconds and loads everything instantly, with a lot of storage!!

-15.6inch FULL HD 1920 x 1080p IPS matte display, graphics are beautiful, very high color accuracy, and IPS technology.

-Red Backlit keyboard

-CD/DVD, HDMI, USB 3.0, Ethernet, HD webcam, ect

-Intel AC 7265 dual band wireless, one of the fastest wireless adapters, web pages load instantly!!
---------------------------

Very fast Asus gaming laptop, portable with great performance, and expensive upgrades. Great for gaming or school very fast. 
Model is ROG GL552VW.

Was $1700. Asking $750 OBO
</description><zip>t2z1x8</zip><active>0</active></Laptop><Laptop identity="\HP Zbook"><price>680</price><size>15</size><name>HP Zbook 15 Mobile Workstation-- i7-- Quadro- 2tb</name><description>Model is in great condition, no scratches, looks and works like new.
Comes with a fresh install of Windows 10 PRO, 
as well as Microsoft Office 2016 PROFESSIONAL PLUS!!!

Specs are as follows:
--------------------

-Intel Core i7 4800mq @ 2.7 - 3.7ghz QUAD CORE (Very powerful processor)

-Nvidia Quadro k1100m professional workstation graphics, with 2gb dedicated GDDR5 video memory, WILL RUN GAMES ON HIGH SETTINGS!!, designed and optimized for CAD work, very powerful graphics card.

-Intel HD 4600 integrated graphics card for saving battery life, battery is good for 5 HOURS!!!!

-16gb DDR3 ram (A lot of ram, in quad channel mode, very fast)

-UPGRADED 2tb HDD, a lot of storage, it will take years to use all this storage

-15.6inch FULL HD 1920 x 1080p matte display, beautiful screen, very high color accuracy, designed for graphics design.

-CD/DVD, display port, HD webcam, great sounding speakers, dual band AC 7260 wireless, ect

-Backlit keyboard, trackpoint, and fingerprint reader.
--------------------------------

Very powerful HP Zbook laptop, designed for CAD work, but will run games with ease as well. Build quality is amazing, with brushed aluminum chassis, and high end materials.

Great as a gaming laptop.
Originally cost $3000, designed for business usage and graphics design, very reliable fast laptop with great poerformance and amazing battery life,

Asking $680 OBO
</description><zip>t2z1x8</zip><active>0</active></Laptop><Laptop identity="\Acer Aspire"><price>580</price><size>17</size><name>Acer Aspire 17inch GAMING LAPTOP-- Nvidia -- Games on high!!</name><description>Model is in great condition, never had a single problem, will play games on high settings!!

Comes with a fresh install of Windows 10 PRO,
as well as Microsoft OFFICE 2016 PROFESSIONAL PLUS

Specs are as follows:
---------------------------------------------

-Intel Core i5 6200u @ 2.3 - 2.8ghz (Very fast efficient processor)

-Nvidia GeForce 940mx with 2gb dedicated GDDR5 video memory. Usually this card comes with GDDR3 video memory, this one has much faster memory, and better performance. 
WILL RUN GAMES ON MEDIUM/HIGH SETTINGS!!

-Intel HD 520 integrated graphics for saving battery life, battery is good for 4+ hours!!

-12gb DDR4 memory, fastest latest memory

-1tb HDD

-17.3inch HD  ExaColor display, grphics are beautiful

-HDMI, CD/DVD, USB 3.0, USB 3.1 type C, ect.
-----------------------------

Very powerful 17 inch gaming laptop from acer. Very low power usage despite being 17 inches, thin and portable with a large screen, great battery life, and great performance. Consumes at most 65w of power, so it will charge on airplane outlets!!

Perfect for school with the installation of Office 2016.

Model is E5-774G-596Q Aspire E 17, originally cost $1400, 

Asking $580 OBO
</description><zip>t2z1x8</zip><active>0</active></Laptop><Laptop identity="\HP ZBook17"><price>750</price><size>17</size><name>HP ZBook17 --- i7 --32gb ram-- Quadro 4gb-- SSD-- OFFICE 2016</name><description>Model is in great condition, very powerful portable workstation/ gaming laptop !!
Comes with a fresh install of Windows 10 PRO, as well as Microsoft Office 2016 PROFESSIONAL PLUS!!

Also comes with HP bag, and HP 200w genuine charger.

Specs are as follows:
--------------------------------------

-Intel Core i7 4700mq @ 2.4 - 3.4ghz QUAD CORE (Very fast processor)

-Nvidia Quadro k3100m with 4gb dedicated GDDR5 video memory. GAMES ON HIGH!!!, designed for graphical design, and CAD work, excels at games as well!!

-Intel HD 4600 integrated graphics for saving battery life, battery is good for 4-5 hours!!!

-32gb DDR3 ram 4x8gb sticks, in quad channel mode, ram is very fast, and a lot of ram.

-256gb SSD, room for a second HDD/SSD, or m-sata drives. Boots in seconds, and loads everything instantly.

-17.3inch FULL HD 1920 x 1080 matte IPS display, graphics are beautiful, close to 100% color accuracy. Perfect for gaming, or graphics design. Screen is very large with amazing graphics!!

-Sim card slot, to use mobile data

-Backlit keyboard, fingerprint reader, CD/DVD/Bluray combo drive, trackpoint, USB 3.0, HD webcam, ect.

-Aluminum chasis for a very high-end build quality and feel.
------------------------------

Very powerful moblie workstation from HP, one of the best build qualities of any laptop. 

Will run for days and never get hot!! The Quadro k3100m is a very powerful graphics card, designed for graphical design. 4gb dedicated GDDR5 video memory, ensure that any application will never run out of graphical memory.

This laptop excels at CAD work, but will also run games with ease, never breaking a sweat, or getting hot. Built to last a long time!!

32gb of ram and an SSD ensure that everything loads instantly, and will be able to run virtual machines, games, or any intensive program with lots of left over memory.

Great as a gaming laptop / portable workstation. Perfect for school, or work.

Model is Zbook 17

Originally cost $4200, asking $750 OBO
</description><zip>t2z1x8</zip><active>0</active></Laptop><Laptop identity="\Dell Inspiron15"><price>750</price><size>15</size><name>Dell Inspiron15 GAMING LAPTOP-- i7- GTX 960m 4gb-- GAMES ON HIGH</name><description>Model is in great condition, never had a single problem.
Comes with a fresh install of Windows 10

Specs are as follows:
--------------------------------

-Intel Core i7 6700hq @ 2.6 - 3.5ghz QUAD CORE (Very powerful processor)

-Nvidia GeForce GTX 960m with 4gb dedicated GDDR5 video memory!!! GAMES ON HIGH SETTINGS!!! NO LAG!!!

-Intel HD 530 integrated graphics for saving battery life, batteyr is good for 5 hours!!

-8gb ram

-1tb HDD

-15.6inch FULL HD 1920 x 1080p IPS matte display, graphics are beautiful

-Backlit keyboard, USB 3.0, HDMI, Dual band wireless, ect
-------------------------

Very powerful gaming laptop from Dell. Will play games on high settings!! no lag, with a great battery life, and very portable design. 

Perfect for school or travel. 

Model is Inspiron 15-7559

Asking $750 OBO
</description><zip>t2z1x8</zip><active>0</active></Laptop><Laptop identity="\Alienware 14"><price>600</price><size>14</size><name>Alienware 14 GAMING LAPTOP-- Games on high!!</name><description>Model is in good condition, will run games on high!!

Comes with a fresh install of Windows 10 PRO, as well as Microsoft OFFICE 2016 PROFESSIONAL PLUS!!!

Specs are as follows:

-Intel Core i5 4200u @ 2.5 - 3.1ghz (Very fast and low energy usage processor)

-Nvidia GeForce GTX 765m with 2gb dedicated GDDR5 video memory.
Will play games on high settings!!

-Intel HD 4600 integrated graphics for saving battery life, battery is good for 4 hours!!

-8gb ram

-750gb HDD

-14.1 inch HD display, matte.

-Klipsh audio, speaker sound amazing, will easily fill a room.

-Color changing backlit keyboard, and other customizable zones.

-Killer 1202 wireless, very fast wireless card, webpages load instantly!!

-CD/DVD, USB 3.0, HDMI, Killer ethernet, ect
----------------------

Very powerful gaming laptop from Alienware, will run games on high settings, in a portable 14inch chassis.

Perfect for school with the installation of OFFICE 2016, or for travel. 
Amazing build quality, cooling is great, never gets hot.

Model is Alienware 14 r1
Asking $650 OBO
</description><zip>t2z1x8</zip><active>0</active></Laptop><Laptop identity="\Lenovo Yoga2--"><price>440</price><size>14</size><name>Lenovo Yoga2-- 2 in 1-- i5-- 8gb -- 1080p IPS Touch-- </name><description>Model is in great condition, never had a single problem.
Comes with a fresh install of Windows 10 PRO, 
As well as Microsoft OFFICE 2016 PROFESSIONAL PLUS!!

Specs are as follows:
-----------------------

-Intel Core i5 4200U @ 1.6 - 2.6ghz (Fast and efficient processor)

-8gb ram

-Intel HD 4400 graphics.

-13.3inch FULL HD 1920 x 1080p IPS Touch screen!!! Has a glass coating, Graphics are beautiful!!
Screen also rotates 360% to become a powerful tablet.

-500gb hdd

-Intel 7260N wireless, for very fast connection speeds!!

-USB 3.0, HDMI, backlit keyboard, ect
---------------------

Very thin lightweight ultrabook from Lenovo, battery is good for around 5 hours!!!

Perfect for school or work, or any kind of travel, great build quality, and the screen is  beautiful.

Model is Lenovo Yoga 2, originally cost $1300

Asking $440 OBO
</description><zip>T2Z1Z6</zip><active>0</active></Laptop><Laptop identity="\Asus Zenbook"><price>580</price><size>14</size><name>Asus Zenbook Ultrabook-- CoreM-- SSD-- 1080p IPS</name><description>Model is in good condition, never had a single problem.

Comes with a fresh install of Windows 10 PRO
As well as MICROSOFT OFFICE 2016 PROFESSIONAL PLUS

Also comes with original box and packaging

Specs are as follows:
---------------------------------

-Intel Core m3-6Y30 @ .9 - 2.2ghz (Dual core with HyperThreading) Very low emission processor, Fast as well. Designed to be run with out a fan!!

-Intel HD 515 integrated graphics, good for light gaming, i.e. DOTA2, or similar games.

-256gb SSD, boots in seconds, and loads everything instantly

-8gb ram

-13.3inch FULL HD 1920 x 1080p IPS matte display, graphics are beautiful

-Bang &amp; Olufsen speakers

-Intel dual band 7265 wireless, very fast wireless adapter, webpages load instantly!!

-USB 3.0, HDMI, HD webcam, ect
----------------------

One of the thinnest laptops ever made, very light, and powerful.
Laptop does not have a fan which means that it is completely silent, and the battery lasts for around 7 hours!! 

The build quality is amazing, a solid aluminum chassis and amazing screen, very light and sturdy. Weighs around 2 pounds!!

Perfect for school or travel with the thin design and OFFICE 2016 installation.

Model is UX305CA

Sells on Amazon for $1100

Asking $580 OBO
</description><zip>t2z1x8</zip><active>0</active></Laptop><Laptop identity="\Lenovo Y700"><price>650</price><size>15</size><name>Lenovo Y700 GAMING LAPTOP-- Quad core-- 4gb graphics</name><description>Model is in good condition, looks and works like new!!
Will play games on high settings, NO LAG!!

Comes with a fresh install of Windows 10 Home.

Specs are as follows:
------------------------

-AMD FX-8800p @ 2.1 - 3.4ghz QUAD CORE (One of the fastest processors AMD makes, very powerful processor)

-AMD Radeon R9 M385X with 4gb dedicated GDDR5 video memory, very powerful GPU, has the upgraded 4gb option. Will run games on high settings!!

-Integrated AMD R7 graphics with 1gb memory, for saving battery life, battery is good for 5 hours!!!

-16gb ram (a lot of ram)

-1tb hdd 

-15.6 inch FULL HD 1920 x 1080p IPS display, with a matte coating. Graphics are beautiful.

-JBL Audio with built in subwoofer, sound quality is amazing, easily fills an entire room.

-Red Backlit keyboard

-USB 3.0, HDMI, Ethernet, HD webcam, ect

-Metal chassis, and trim, very high end build quality.

-Ac wireless, for very fast wireless data transfer.
---------------------------------

Very powerful gaming laptop from Lenovo. Less than an inch thin, and capable of running games on high, with an amazing battery life. 
Great build quaility, and looks great.

Originally cost $1400 a year ago.

Model is Y700 15-ACZ

Asking $650 OBO
</description><zip>t2z1x8</zip><active>0</active></Laptop><Laptop identity="\Alienware 13r2"><price>750</price><size>14</size><name>Alienware 13r2 GAMING LAPTOP-- SSD-- GTX 960m-- GAMES ON HIGH!!</name><description>Model is in mint condition, has had the protective crocodile skin on since it was purchased. Installed professionally, and easy to remove.

Plays games on high settings, NO LAG!!

Comes with a fresh install of Windows 10 PRO (Genuine), and original box (no packaging)

---------------------------------

Specs are as follows:

-Intel Core i5 6200u @ 2.3 -2.8ghz (Very powerful efficient processor)

-Nvidia GeForce GTX 960m with 2gb dedicated GDDR5 video memory, WILL RUN GAMES ON HIGH SETTINGS!! Very powerful graphics card.

-Intel HD520 integrated graphics card for saving battery life, battery is good for 4-5hours!!

-16gb ram (a lot of ram)

-256gb Samsung SSD, one of the fastest SSDs in the market, boots in seconds, and loads everything instantly!

-Atheros Killer wireless 1535ac. (one of the fastest wireless cards ever made, loads webpages instantly, very low latency, great for gaming).

-HDMI, Thunderbolt, usb 3.0, ect

-Klipsh audio, speakers are amazing for such a small laptop, easily fills a room.

-13.3inch HD matte screen, beautiful graphics

-Color changing led backlit keyboard, and other zones.
--------------------

Very powerful gaming laptop from Alienware, very portable with great build quality high end specs.
Perfect for school, or travel, or gaming on the go.

Originally cost $1600. still in mint condition!!

Asking $750 OBO
</description><zip>t2z1x8</zip><active>0</active></Laptop><Laptop identity="\Lenovo Flex15"><price>650</price><size>15</size><name>Lenovo Flex15 --- i7-- GAMING-- 1080p IPS-- Touchscreen</name><description>Good for gaming!!! Model is in mint condition, looks and works like new!!!
Comes with a fresh install of Windows 10 Home, as well as Microsoft OFFICE 2016 PROFESSIONAL PLUS
(Latest and best version of Office)

Specs are as follows
---------------------------------

-Intel Core i7 6500u @ 2.5 - 3.1ghz!! (Very powerful processor, 6th generation i7)

-Nvidia GeForce gt 940m with 2gb dedicated video memory, good for gaming!!! Will run games on medium/high settings!!! Very powerful graphics card!!

-Intel hd 520 integrated graphics for saving battery life, battery is good for 4-5 hours!!

-8gb ram

-1tb hdd

-15.6inch Full HD 1920 x 1080p IPS screen, glossy. Full touch screen, and fold 360degrees to become a tablet!! Graphics are beautiful, screen has close to 100% color accuracy and uses IPS technology for amazing graphics!!

-Backlit keyboard

-USB 3.0, HDMI, ethernet, dual band wireless, ect
---------------------------

Very powerful lenovo laptop, very light and thin with great performance, and great battery life.
The screen is beauitful, and is one of the nicest screens on the market, and its a touch screen!!

Model is Lenovo Flex 3 1580

Originally cost $1400, asking $650 OBO
</description><zip>t2z1x8</zip><active>1</active></Laptop><Laptop identity="\HP Envy17--"><price>480</price><size>17</size><name>HP Envy17-- i7-- HD Touch screen--- 12gb ram-- OFFICE 2016</name><description>Model is in great condition, looks and works like new. Never had a single problem.

Comes with a fresh install of Windows 10 PRO, AS WELL AS Microsoft OFFICE 2016 PROFESSIONAL PLUS
(Latest and best versoin of the Office software suite).

Specs are as follows:
------------------------------

-Intel Core i7 4710HQ @ 2.5 - 3.5ghz QUAD CORE (Very powerful i7 processor)

-12gb ram

-Intel HD 4600 integrated graphics, good for light gaming.

-1tb HDD

-17.3inch HD WLED Touch Screen, glossy. Graphics are beautiful!!

-Backlit keyboard

-CD/DVD, USB 3.0, HDMI, fingerprint reader, dual band wireless.

-Beats Audio speakers, with built in subwoofer. One of the best speaker system ever put in a laptop. Easily fills a room!!
--------------------------------------

Very powerful 17inch laptop from HP, High end build quality, with beautiful graphics, amazing audio, and 3-4 hour battery life!!!

Thin, and portable with a very large screen.

Model is HP ENVY 17-k073ca

Originally cost $1350, Asking $480 OBO
</description><zip>t2z1x8</zip><active>0</active></Laptop><Laptop identity="\ASUS Vivobook"><price>320</price><size>15</size><name>ASUS Vivobook Flip--- i5 6th gen-- 1080p Touch Screen</name><description>Everything works fine, no issues ever. 
A few scratches and scuffs on the back and bottom, screen is scratch free. 
These scratches do not affect anything, and are purely cosmetic.
Price reflects this.

Comes with a fresh install of Windows 10 PRO, 
as well as Microsoft OFFICE 2016 PROFESSIONAL PLUS

Specs are as follows:
----------------------

-Intel Core i5 6200u @ 2.3 -2.8ghz

-8gb ram

-Intel hd520 integrated graphics, good for light gaming.

-15.6inch FULL HD 1920 x 1080p glossy display. Touch Screen, and fold 360 degrees to become a tablet!!

-1tb hdd

-USB 3.0, HDMI, Ethernet, USB-c.
-------------------------------

Very thin powerful laptop from Asus. Beautiful touchscreen full 1080p, and becomes a tablet. 
High end build quality with brushed aluminum case.

Perfect as a cheap laptop for school or travel, very thin and portable, and comes with full Office 2016 installation.

Originally cost $1150 a year ago

Model is Vivobook Flip TP501UA

Asking $320 OBO
</description><zip>t2z1x8</zip><active>0</active></Laptop><Laptop identity="\Acer AspireE5--"><price>520</price><size>17</size><name>Acer AspireE5-- 17inch gaming laptop-- Nvidia --1080p</name><description>Model is in great condition,
Comes with a fresh install of Windows 10 PRO
As well as Microsoft Office 2016 Professional PLUS

Specs are as follows:
---------------------

-Intel core i5 5200u @ 2.2 -2.7ghz (Very powerful processor)

-Nvidia GeForce GT 940m with 2gb dedicated video memory!!! Plays games on medium/high settings!!

-Intel HD 5500 integrated graphics for saving battery life, battery is good for 4-5 hours!!

-8gb ram

-1tb HDD (1000gb) A lot of storage

-17.3inch FULL HD 1920 x 1080p matte display, LED backlit. Graphics are beautiful, screen has a very high color accuracy

-CD/DVD HDMI, USB 3.0, dual band wireless, HD webcam, ect
-----------------------

Very powerful 17 inch laptop from Acer, thin and light with great performance and amazing graphics.

Good for portable power and gaming on the go. 
Perfect for school with the installation of OFFICE 2016, and great battery life.

Model is E5-772G

Originally cost $1200 a year ago. Asking $520 OBO
</description><zip>t2z1x8</zip><active>0</active></Laptop><Laptop identity="\ASUS ROG"><price>700</price><size>17</size><name>ASUS ROG GAMING LAPTOP-- i7-- SSD-- GAMES ON ULTRA!!</name><description>Model is in mint condition, looks and works like new!!! Never had a single problem.

Comes with a fresh install of Windows 10 PRO, as well as Microsoft OFFICE 2016 PROFESSIONAL PLUS (Latest and best version of Office software suite)

Specs are as follows:
---------------

-Intel Core i7 4700HQ @ 2.4 - 3.4ghz QUAD CORE (Very powerful quad-core processor)

-16gb ram

-Nvidia GeForce GTX 780m with 4gb dedcated GDDR5 video memory, WILL PLAY GAMES ON HIGH/ULTRA SETTINGS!!! NO LAG!!. Very powerful GPU.

-256gb SSD + 750gb HDD, Boots in around 3 seconds, load everything instantly

-Atheros Killer 1202-n wireless, one of the fastest wireless adapters on the market, loads webpages instantly!!

-17.3inch FULL HD 1920 x 1080p matte display,graphics are beautiful, screen has a very high color accuracy!!

-CD/DVD/Bluray combo drive

-Backlit keyboard

-HDMI, USB 3.0, Ethernet, card-reader, HD webcam, ect.

-Build-in subwoofer for amazing sound quality, speakers sound amazing!! Easily fills a room!!
----------------

Very powerful Asus Rog Gaming laptop. High end built quality with brushed aluminum finish and metal chassis.  Great cooling system, ensures laptop doesn't get hot while playing games.

Will play games on high settings, no lag. Perfect for school with the installation of Office 2016.

Model is G750jh with max specs.
Originally cost $3200

Asking $700 OBO
</description><zip>t2z1x8</zip><active>0</active></Laptop><Laptop identity="\Acer Aspire14--"><price>540</price><size>14</size><name>Acer Aspire14-- Gaming laptop-- Nvidia 940m -- 8gb ram-- 1tb</name><description>Model is in good condition, never had a single problem.
Comes with a fresh install of Windows 10 PRO
As well as Microsoft OFFICE 2016 PROFESSIONAL PLUS!! (Latest and best versino of the Office software suite)

Specs are as follows:

-Intel Core i5 6200u @ 2.3 -2.8ghz (Fast and efficient processor)

-Nvidia GeForce GT 940m with 2gb dedicated video memory, WILL PLAY GAMES ON MEDIUM\HIGH SETTINGS!!

-Intel HD520 integrated graphics for saving battery life, battery is good for 6 hours!!!

-8gb ram

-1tb HDD (1000gb)

-14inch HD screen, glossy. Graphics are sharp with high color accuracy.

-Dual Band wireless, HMDI, USB 3.0, HD webcam, ect
------------------------

Very thin light weight gaming laptop from Acer. 
Powerful laptop with a great dedicated video card, and efficient processor/graphics.
6 Hour battery life and able to play games on high settings!!


Perfect for school with the installation of Office 2016, and amazing battery life.

Model is E5-474G-50UT

Originally cost $1100 a year ago. Asking $540 OBO
</description><zip>t2z1x8</zip><active>1</active></Laptop></ads>